[ 
      {
        "question": "QUESTION 1.",
        "choice1": "laddoo",
        "choice2": "jalebi",
        "choice3": "burfi ",
        "choice4": "None of these",
        "answer": "3"
      },
      {
        "question": "QUESTION 2.​",
        "choice1": "Please help for some time",
        "choice2": "Please wait for this time",
        "choice3": "hey, wait for some time",
        "choice4": "Please wait for some time",
        "answer": "4"
      },
      {
        "question": "QUESTION 3.",
        "choice1": "23",
        "choice2": "24",
        "choice3": "20",
        "choice4": "15",
        "answer": "2"
      },
      {
        "question": "QUESTION 4 ",
        "choice1": "the carrier in full",
        "choice2": "your employment with in",
        "choice3": "carrier all in all",
        "choice4": "your carrier with all​",
        "answer": "4"
      },
      {
        "question": "QUESTION​ 5",
        "choice1": "Do-While loop",
        "choice2": "While loop",
        "choice3": "For loop",
        "choice4": "NOne of these",
        "answer": "1"
      },
      {
        "question": "QUESTION 6",
        "choice1": "visited",
        "choice2": "visites",
        "choice3": "going",
        "choice4": "None of these",
        "answer": "1"
      },
      {
        "question": "QUESTION 7 ",
        "choice1": "Cu+",
        "choice2": "Li+",
        "choice3": "Ag+",
        "choice4": "Au+",
        "answer": "2"
      },
      {
        "question": "QUESTION 8",
        "choice1": "289/5",
        "choice2": "89/50",
        "choice3": "289/50",
        "choice4": "209/50",
        "answer": "3"
      },
      {
        "question": "QUESTION 9",
        "choice1": "High current carrying capacity",
        "choice2": "Higher Voltage",
        "choice3": " Higher Power",
        "choice4": "none of the above",
        "answer": "3"
      },
      {
        "question": "QUESTION 10",
        "choice1": "71",
        "choice2": "72",
        "choice3": "73",
        "choice4": "74",
        "answer": "1"
      },
      {
        "question": "QUESTION: 11",
        "choice1": "MlP",
        "choice2": "NTR",
        "choice3": "MSP",
        "choice4": "NTO",
        "answer": "3"
      },
      {
        "question": "QUESTION 12",
        "choice1": " Process Activities ",
        "choice2": "Process Roles",
        "choice3": "Process Policy ",
        "choice4": "All of these are elements of a process",
        "answer": "4"
      },
      {
        "question": "QUESTION 13",
        "choice1": "Cash A/c … Dr      - 90000 To Capital A/c      -       90000",
        "choice2": "Cash A/c … Dr      - 90000 To Capital A/c",
        "choice3": "Cash A/c … Dr,To Capital A/c      -       90000",
        "choice4": "None of these",
        "answer": "1"
      },
      {
        "question": "QUESTION 14",
        "choice1": "Carrot ",
        "choice2": "Radish ",
        "choice3": "Turnip ",
        "choice4": "Potato",
        "answer": "4"
      },
      {
        "question": "QUESTION 15",
        "choice1": "Completing the syllabus without ascertaining the learning of children",
        "choice2": "Learning levels of children ",
        "choice3": "Class",
        "choice4": "grade of the child Age of the child",
        "answer": "1"
      },
      {
        "question": "QUESTION 16",
        "choice1": " services enables rapid disaster recovery",
        "choice2": "Optimized for data for which retrieval times of several hours are suitable.",
        "choice3": " Optimized for data that is infrequently accessed.",
        "choice4": " Secure and durable storage for data archiving and backup.",
        "answer": "2"
      },
      {
        "question": "QUESTION 17",
        "choice1": "hardly",
        "choice2": "proudly",
        "choice3": "correctly",
        "choice4": "None of these",
        "answer": "1"
      },
      {
        "question": "QUESTION 18",
        "choice1": "ClF3",
        "choice2": "BCl3",
        "choice3": "SO3",
        "choice4": "XeO3",
        "answer": "4"
      },
      {
        "question": "QUESTION 19 ",
        "choice1": "wreaked",
        "choice2": "reeked",
        "choice3": "wreckt",
        "choice4": "rect",
        "answer": "1"
      },
      {
        "question": "QUESTION 20",
        "choice1": "She requested be bring in glass of water.",
        "choice2": "She requested to bring a glass of water.",
        "choice3": "She request to bring a glass the water.",
        "choice4": "None of these",
        "answer": "2"
      }
  ]